- I like to swing right out of that tune
and jump right in to the next one,
a song I wrote myself,
mostly here and partially
in the United States, too.
(guitar playing begins)
♪ Just yesterday morning they
let me know you were gone ♪
♪ Suzanne, the plans they
made put an end to you ♪
♪ I walked out on the morning
and I wrote down this song ♪
♪ I just can't remember
who to send it to ♪
♪ I've seen fire and I've seen rain ♪
♪ I've seen sunny days that
I thought would never end ♪
♪ I've seen lonely times when
I could not find a friend ♪
♪ But I always thought
that I'd see you again ♪
♪ Won't you look down upon me, Jesus ♪
♪ You've got to help me make a stand ♪
♪ You've just got to see
me through another day ♪
♪ My body's aching and
my time is at hand ♪
♪ And I won't make it any other way ♪
♪ I've seen fire and I've seen rain ♪
♪ I've seen sunny days that
I thought would never end ♪
♪ I've seen lonely times when
I could not find a friend ♪
♪ But I always thought
that I'd see you again ♪
♪ I've been walking my
mind to an easy time ♪
♪ With my back turned towards the sun ♪
♪ Lord knows when the cold wind blows ♪
♪ It'll turn your head around, now ♪
♪ There's hours of time
on the telephone line ♪
♪ To talk about things to come ♪
♪ Sweet dreams and flying
machines in pieces on the ground ♪
♪ Whoa now, I've seen
fire and I've seen rain ♪
♪ I've seen sunny days that
I thought would never end ♪
♪ I've seen lonely times when
I could not find a friend ♪
♪ But I always thought that I'd see you, ♪
♪ Somehow, one more time again, now ♪
♪ I thought I'd see you
one more time again ♪
♪ There's just a few things
coming my way this time around ♪
♪ Whoa now, I thought I'd see you, ♪
♪ I thought I'd see you, fire and rain ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
(audience applauds)